<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollApp3</string>
    <string name="textview">
          <b>“Ever loved someone so much, you would do anything for them? Yeah, well make that someone yourself and do whatever the hell you want.”</b> \n\n

        <b>“Work until you no longer have to introduce yourself.” </b>\n\n

       <b> “When you\’re backed against the wall, break the goddamn thing down.”</b>\n\n

        <b>“The only time success comes before work is in the dictionary.”</b>\n\n

       <b> “Winners don\’t make excuses when the other side plays the game.”</b>\n\n

       <b> “Sorry, I can\’t hear you over the sound of how awesome I am.”</b>\n\n

       <b> “Wine is not a magic serum of truth. It just silences that smart little voice in your head which advises against saying some dumb                shit.”</b>\n\n

        <b>“It’s going to happen because I\’m going to make it happen.”

        “I like to smile at people who don\’t like me.”\n\n

        “Don\’t raise your voice, improve your argument.”\n\n

            “Goals so big you get uncomfortable telling small minded people.”\n\n

            “Win a no-win situation by rewriting the rules.”\n\n

    “Let them hate. Just make sure they spell your name right.”\n\n
             “I could agree with you but then we\’d both be wrong.” – Harvey Specter\n\n

    “Winners don\’t make excuses.” – Harvey Specter\n\n
            “When people you don’t even know hate you, that\’s when you know you\’re the best.” – Harvey Specter\n\n

 “If they think you care, they\’ll walk all over you.”\n\n

    “If you kinda sorta try, then you kinda sorta fail.” – Harvey Specter\n\n

     “I don\’t play the odds, I play the man.” – Harvey Specter\n\n

        “You want to change your life? Change the way you think.”\n\n
        As he read, I fell in love the way you fall asleep: slowly, and then all at once.\n\n
    It seemed like forever ago, like we\'ve had this brief but still infinite forever. Some infinities are bigger than other infinities.\n\n
    You don\'t get to choose if you get hurt in this world, old man, but you do have some say in who hurts you.\n\n
    My thoughts are stars I can\'t fathom into constellations.\n\n
    It\'s a metaphor, see: You put the killing thing right between your teeth, but you don\'t give it the power to do its killing.\n\n
    What a treacherous thing to believe that a person is more than a person.\n\n
    Y\'all smoke to enjoy it. I smoke to die.\n\n
    What is the point of being alive if you don\’t at least try to do something remarkable?\n\n
    Margo always loved mysteries. And in everything that came afterward, I could never stop thinking that maybe she loved mysteries so much that she became one.\n\n
    Grief does not change you, Hazel. It reveals you.\n\n
            that if people were rain, I was drizzle and she was a hurricane.”
</b>
    </string>
</resources>